Guide to the C. D. Wright Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
C. D. Wright papers
1923-2012
YCAL MSS 820
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
38.34
(55 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
The C. D. Wright papers consists of correspondence, writings, notebooks, and printed and other material relating chiefly to Wright's literary and professional activities. There is correspondence from writers, artists, literary scholars, family, and friends. Named correspondents include Mei-Mei Berssenbrugge, Forrest Gander, Peter Gizzi, W. S. Merwin, Michael Ondaatje, Keith and Rosmarie Waldrop, Marjorie Welish, and Elizabeth Willis, among others. The writings include drafts, proofs, and other material for several works dating from the 1990s onward. Works include: Tremble (1996), DeepStep Come Shining (1998), Steal Away (2002), One Big Step (2003), Cooling Time (2005), and Rising, Falling, Hovering (2008). Other materials found in the collection include: notebooks and research material; printed material, including clippings, publicity, reviews, and issues of journals; computer files, including drafts of writings and copies of email; audiovisual materials, including sound recordings and photographs; records of the journal Lost Roads; legal records, including contracts and permissions; and documentation relating to other literary and academic matters, such as awards, conferences and other events, and blurbs and recommendations.
Wright, C. D., 1949-2016
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired by gift and purchase, 2007-2012. For more information consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 26-27, 32, and 56 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 55 (audiovisual material): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
C. D. Wright (1949-)
Carolyn D. Wright was born in Mountain Home, Arkansas and educated at Memphis State College (now the University of Memphis) and at the University of Arkansas. She has published numerous volumes of poetry, including: Translation of the Gospel Back into Tongues (1981); Further Adventures with You (1986); String Light (1991), which won the Poetry Center Book Award; Tremble (1996); Deepstep Come Shining (1998); Steal Away: New and Selected Poems (2002); One Big Self: Prisoners of Louisiana (2003), with photographer Deborah Luster; Cooling Time: An American Poetry Vigil (2005); and Rising, Falling, Hovering (2008), which won the Griffin Poetry Prize.
In addition to the Witter Bynner Prize and a Whiting Award, she has received fellowships from the National Endowment for the Arts, the Guggenheim Foundation, the Bunting Institute, and the Lannan Foundation. With her husband, poet Forrest Gander, she edits Lost Roads Publishers. Wright teaches at Brown University.
Biographical information taken from the Academy of American Poets, Biographies of American Poets.
Scope and Contents
The C. D. Wright papers consists of correspondence, writings, notebooks, and printed and other material relating chiefly to Wright's literary and professional activities. There is correspondence from writers, artists, literary scholars, family, and friends. Named correspondents in the Collection Contents list below include Mei-Mei Berssenbrugge, Forrest Gander, Peter Gizzi, W. S. Merwin, Michael Ondaatje, Keith and Rosmarie Waldrop, Marjorie Welish, and Elizabeth Willis, among others. The writings include drafts, proofs, and other material for several works dating from the 1990s onward. Works include: Tremble (1996), Deepstep Come Shining (1998), Steal Away (2002), One Big Step (2003), Cooling Time (2005), and Rising, Falling, Hovering (2008). Other materials found in the collection include: notebooks and research material; printed material, including clippings, publicity, reviews, and issues of journals; computer files, including drafts of writings and copies of email; audiovisual materials, including sound recordings and photographs; records of the journal Lost Roads; legal records, including contracts and permissions; and documentation relating to other literary and academic matters, such as awards, conferences and other events, and blurbs and recommendations.
Arrangement
Organized into four groupings: I. January 2007 Acquisition. II. January 2007 Addition. III. August 2012 Acquisition. IV. October 2012 Acquisition.
American literature -- 20th Century; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Electronic documents; Photographic prints; Sound recordings; Poets -- United States -- 20th Century; Berssenbrugge, Mei-mei, 1947-; Gander, Forrest, 1956-; Gizzi, Peter, 1959-; Merwin, W. S. (William Stanley), 1927-; Ondaatje, Michael, 1943-; Waldrop, Keith, 1932-; Waldrop, Rosmarie, 1935-; Welish, Marjorie, 1944-; Willis, Elizabeth; Wright, C. D., 1949-2016; Lost Roads Publishers
- January 2007 Acquisition, 1955-2006; 17.58; (26 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Scope and Contents
  Boxes 26-27 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Organized into eleven subgroupings: Correspondence with Writers, Artists; Correspondence with Writers, Other Artists, Some Students, Family, Friends; Correspondence, Students/Writers; Correspondence, Family, Friends (Memphis and Fayetteville), Some Writers, Artists; CD MSS B202 #13; Old Writing Matter; CD Files from File Cabinet; One Big Self, CD 2006; Mixed Office (Bran) Files; Notebooks; and Miscellaneous Papers.
  The 2007 January acquisition contains correspondence, writings, notebooks, and printed and other materials, including computer files, relating chiefly to C. D. Wright's literary and professional activities.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 939.
  Acquired by gift and purchase, 2007. For more information, see the appropriate curator.
  - Correspondence with Writers, Artists
    - Artists, 1990-2005, undated (Box 1)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1991-2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Barg, Barbara, 1978, undated (Box 1)
    - Burt, Steve, 1997-2000, undated (Box 1)
    - Booth, Philip, 1985-1996, undated (Box 1)
    - Canfield, 1991-1993, undated (Box 1)
    - Coover, Robert, 1989-1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Dent, Tory, 1981-1998, undated (Box 1)
    - Ducornet, Rikki, 1990-1993, undated (Box 1)
    - Duvernet, Kay, 1987-2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Forche, Carolyn, 1996-2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Gilfillan, Merrill, 1992-2005, undated (Box 1)
    - Gizzi, Peter; Willis, Elizabeth, 1992-2000, undated (Box 1)
    - Goodman, Jenny, 1990-2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Harper, Michael, 1983-2001, undated (Box 1)
    - Henrikson, Laura Wilson, 1994-1996 (Box 1)
    - Hix, Harvey L., 1995-2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Holman, Bob, 1990-1996 (Box 1)
    - Larzer, Hank, 1990-2000 (Box 1)
    - Leonin, Mia, 1994-1998, undated (Box 1)
    - Lisker, Emily, 1991-1998, undated (Box 1)
    - Luster, Deborah, 1997, undated (Box 1)
    - Mayes, Frances, 1993-2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Merwin, W.S., 1980-1999, undated (Box 1)
    - Ondaatje, Michael, 1990-2005, undated (Box 1)
    - Ray, Amy, undated (Box 1)
    - Rosenwasser, Rena, 1990-1997, undated (Box 1)
    - Shapiro, David, 1993-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Sze, Arthur, 2000-2002, undated (Box 2)
    - Taggart, John, 1994-1997, undated (Box 2)
    - Tietz, Ward, 1992-2002, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Truitt, Sam, 1994-1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Van Buren, E., 1992-1995 (Box 2)
    - The Waldrops, 1992, undated (Box 2)
    - Welish, Marjorie, 1991-1999, undated (Box 2)
    - Wellman, Mac, 2001-2003 (Box 2)
    - Writers, 1990-2005, undated (Box 2)
  - Correspondence with Writers, Other Artists, Some Students, Family, Friends
    - Writers and artists, 1990-2005, undated; 4 (Box 2)
    - Writers, artists, friends, 1990-2005, undated (Box 2)
    - Writers and artists A-L, 1981-1999, undated (Box 2)
    - Writers and artists M-, 1990-2005, undated (Box 2)
    - Barg poem, 1978-1999 (Box 3)
    - Friends, 1989-2000, undated (Box 3)
    - Wright, Warren W., 1983-1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Family, 1973-2005, undated; 5 (Box 3)
    - Arkansas, 1985-1990, undated (Box 3)
    - Gander, Forrest, 1983-1986, undated; 2 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, Students/Writers
    - A-D, 1986-2005, undated; 2 (Box 4)
    - E-G, 1985-2005, undated (Box 4)
    - H-L, 1985-2001, undated (Box 4)
    - M-O, 1986-2005, undated (Box 4)
    - P-S, 1985-2005, undated (Box 4)
    - S-Z, 1984-2005, undated (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, student, 1990-2005 (Box 4)
    - Writers, 1986-2001, undated (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, Family, Friends (Memphis and Fayetteville), Some Writers, Artists
    - Some writers, artists, 2000-2006, undated (Box 4)
    - Fayetteville - friends, 1983-1989, undated; 4 (Box 4)
    - Friends - Memphis, 1983-1989, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Friends - Harrison, 1975-1989, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Family, 1965-1989, undated; 8 (Box 5)
  - CD MSS B202 #13
    - Essays, not included in collection, 1990-1993, undated (Box 6)
    - Brown University papers, 1986-1991
    - Miscellaneous magazines, 1985-1996 (Box 6)
    - Bunting Institute paper, undated (Box 6)
    - Further Adventures with You, 1986; 2 (Box 6)
    - Scratch Music, undated (Box 6)
    - Terrorism, 1978 (Box 6)
    - String Light, undated (Box 6)
    - Alla Breve Loving, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Essays uncollected, undated (Box 6)
    - Essays, 1978-1990 (Box 6)
    - CD 1st year, undated (Box 6)
    - Preview, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1990-1993
    - The Woman Who Loved Blue Duck, undated (Box 6)
    - Cooling Time, undated; 3 (Box 6)
    - Out There, undated (Box 6)
    - Invisible City, String Light, 1980-1991 (Box 6)
    - Tremble, undated (Box 7)
    - Just Whistle, 1993; 4 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous notes and postcards, 1962-1989, undated (Box 7)
  - Old Writing Matter
    - Copyright and printing forms re: Alla Breve Loving, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
    - Work correspondence, 1977-1995; 11 (Box 7)
    - Work correspondence, 1976-1985 (Box 8)
    - Picnic/song - treatment/film, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Poetry Center 1980, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
    - Johnson/Franklin on photography, 1986, undated (Box 8)
    - SUNY, 1981-1987, undated (Box 8)
    - Manuscript history, 1979-1982, undated (Box 8)
    - Translation of the gospel back into tongues, undated (Box 8)
  - CD Files from File Cabinet
    - Awards, fellowships, honors, 1983-1995, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Bunting, 1991-1992 (Box 8)
    - Bunting/Guggenheim, 1987-1989 (Box 8)
    - Carnegie Mellon/Costanzo, 1985-1988, undated (Box 8)
    - Books collected for map, 2000, undated (Box 8)
    - Notes, poems, undated (Box 8)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 8)
    - Interview transcript, undated (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8)
    - Humanities grant, 1998-2000; 2 (Box 8)
    - Press, 1998, August 12 (Box 8)
    - Cooling Time, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Essays, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Selected TS (Ryang), 1982-1996, undated (Box 8)
    - Cooling Time, draft, undated (Box 8)
    - Mix of Two Cooling Time, whole drafts, undated; 2 (Box 9)
    - Estimates, 1998-1999, undated (Box 9)
    - Steal Away, 2001 September (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, map, 1999-2000, undated (Box 9)
    - Spanish notebook, undated (Box 9)
    - Memoir, undated; 2 (Box 9)
    - Tremble, press, undated (Box 9)
  - CD Misc.
    - Loose leaves of poetry, undated (Box 9)
    - Deep Step, 1997, undated; 3 (Box 9)
    - Barataria #2, undated
    - Notebooks, undated; 5 (Box 9)
    - Cooling Time, undated; 2 (Box 9)
    - Peru, etc., 1999, undated (Box 9)
    - TIME magazine, 1989-1992 (Box 9)
    - State poet, 1997-2000, undated (Box 9)
    - 2000 Writing Matters, 1999-2000 (Box 9)
    - Nina and other writing projects, 1990-1995 (Box 9)
    - Writing materials, 1995-1999, undated; 3 (Box 10)
    - Abrams book, art/poetry textbook, 1999, undated (Box 10)
    - Press packet/CD/Georgia/original, 1990-1992, undated (Box 10)
    - Breadloaf, 1996-1997, undated (Box 10)
    - Conjunctions, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Of the Mulberry family, undated (Box 10)
    - Approach to Prayer - Nina, 1994, undated (Box 10)
    - The Passenger, 1995, undated (Box 10)
    - Ark articles, 1990-1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Five Fingers Contrib. Ed., 1991-1995, undated (Box 10)
    - Black Warrior, 1997-1998 (Box 10)
    - CD Wright, Alias Theater, 1998, undated (Box 10)
    - Ode/essay, undated (Box 10)
    - Russian translations, 1989-1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Essay on Form, AWP, 1989-1990, undated (Box 10)
    - Essay on the Battlefield, Ironwood, undated (Box 10)
    - Essay on M. Williams, 1980-1989, undated (Box 10)
    - Russia, 1987-1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Art, 1979-1997, undated (Box 10)
    - Film, 1978-1984, undated (Box 10)
    - Music/dance theater, 1978-1988, undated (Box 10)
  - One Big Self, CD 2006
    - Burt, One Big Self, undated (Box 10)
    - One Big Self gallery pamphlets, undated (Box 10)
    - Angola - news clippings re: crime, 1995-2006, undated; 2 (Box 10)
    - Brick, literary journal, fall, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Turnrow, Spring, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Cooling Time, Dorothea Lange - Paul Taylor Prize, 2001, undated (Box 11)
    - One Big Self exhibition, reviews, costs, expenses, 2003-2005 (Box 11)
    - OBS, 2005, undated; 6 (Box 11)
    - Twin Palms, 2001-2002, undated (Box 11)
    - OBS /current distribution, 2000-2003, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - OBS (news/intact), undated (Box 11)
    - OBS verse, undated (Box 11)
    - Loose correspondence with Joe Knight, 2005 (Box 11)
    - OBS ms, undated (Box 11)
    - OBS working version, undated (Box 11)
    - OBS gallery pamphlets, undated (Box 11)
    - OBS inmate correspondence etc., 1998-2005; 5 (Box 11)
    - Note from original box, 2006 November 21 (Box 11)
  - Mixed Office (Bran) Files
    - Lannan Award, 1999-2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Awards, 1986-2001 (Box 12)
    - U of A Distinguished Alum, 1998-1999, undated (Box 12)
    - Dorothea Lange - Paul Taylor Prize, 2000-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Amer. Lit. Assn., 1999-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Poetry society chapbook, 2003, undated (Box 12)
    - Kilometer Zero, 2002, undated (Box 12)
    - Magnitude, 2001-2002, undated (Box 12)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1997-2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Come Shining: The Spiritual South, 1958-1999, undated (Box 12)
    - Buford, New Yorker, 2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Tremble, reviews, 1996-1998, undated (Box 12)
    - Tremble, 1992-1995, undated (Box 12)
    - C.D. Wright, 1983-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Teri Grimm on Deepstep, 1999 (Box 12)
    - Copper Canyon Deepstep, 1995-2005, undated (Box 12)
    - har (related to terrorism articles), 2001 (Box 12)
    - Current writing matters, 1998-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - One Big Self rev. for TX, 2001 (Box 12)
    - U Texas, 1995-2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Jobs, 1998-2000, undated (Box 13)
    - U of Arkansas Press, 1996, undated (Box 13)
    - Spain, etc., 2001, undated (Box 13)
    - Hoerman, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
    - Poetry Flash, 1994-1995, undated (Box 13)
    - Holman interview, 2002, undated (Box 13)
    - Jacket #15 interview, 2001 December (Box 13)
    - Reviews CD, 1979-1987 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence and drafts, 1955-1997, undated (Box 13)
    - Photocopies and printouts of articles, 1994-1997, undated (Box 13)
    - Georgia / String Light, 1990-1993, undated (Box 13)
    - Tremble, reviews, 1997-2000 (Box 13)
    - String Light, reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 13)
    - Just Whistle, 1990-1994, undated (Box 13)
    - Deepstep, 1998-2000, undated; 2 (Box 13)
    - Just Whistle, poems, 1993, undated (Box 13)
    - Washington Square Films, 1990-2001, undated (Box 13)
    - Anthologies, 1980-1998, undated (Box 13)
    - cont. Anthos outdoing, undated (Box 13)
    - Residencies, etc, 1993-2001, undated (Box 13)
    - Bio note, undated (Box 14)
    - RISCA, undated (Box 14)
    - Contracts, 1991-1996, undated (Box 14)
    - ECCO, 1995-1997, undated (Box 14)
    - Critical/gen reviewing/bio, 1994, undated (Box 14)
  - Notebooks
    - Notebooks, undated; 22 (Box 14)
    - Notebooks and diaries, 1978-1998, undated; 17 (Box 15)
    - Notes and fragments, 1985, undated (Box 15)
    - Greenfield Recorder - Gazette, 1957 September 6
    - Folder of notes (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous Papers
    - Fliers, letters, pamphlets, 1984-2000, undated; 3 (Box 16)
    - 2001, 2001, undated (Box 16)
    - 2000, 2000, undated (Box 16)
    - 1999, 1999-2000, undated; 2 (Box 16)
    - 1998, 1998, undated (Box 16)
    - 1997, 1997, undated (Box 16)
    - 1996, 1996, undated (Box 16)
    - 1995, 1991-1995, undated (Box 16)
    - 1994, 1994, undated (Box 16)
    - 1993, 1993, undated (Box 16)
    - 1992, 1992, undated (Box 16)
    - 1991, undated (Box 16)
    - 1990, 1990, undated (Box 16)
    - 1989, 1989, undated (Box 16)
    - 1987, 1986-1988 (Box 16)
    - 1986, 1986, undated (Box 16)
    - 1984, 1984, undated (Box 16)
    - 1983, 1983, undated (Box 16)
    - Undated, 1988, undated (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets, fliers, undated (Box 17)
    - Newspapers, printed material, 1986-2001, undated; 3 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1992-1998, undated (Box 17)
    - Addresses, 1993-1998, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Words and music, 2002 (Box 17)
    - On photography, 1995-2005, undated (Box 17)
    - Files from LRP, 1994-1997, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Recent LRP, 1994-1997, undated (Box 17)
    - University of Arkansas, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Exhibitor project, undated (Box 17)
    - The Lost Roads Project text, undated (Box 17)
    - Project description, undated (Box 17)
    - Maps, undated (Box 17)
    - Lila Wallace, 1992-1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Publications, 1988-1997, undated (Box 17)
    - Arkansas, 1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Historical maps of Arkansas, 1993, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Historical atlas of Arkansas, undated (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Exhibit instructions, undated (Box 17)
    - Computer files, 1987-2006; (108 computer disks) (Box 17)
      Computer disks are restricted. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      2007-ycal-4686-0001: Lila Wallace 3a copy of 2
      2007-ycal-4686-0002: Lila Wallace 2 updated
      2007-ycal-4686-0003: LR Project
      2007-ycal-4686-0004: Lila Wallace
      2007-ycal-4686-0005: Lost Roads Project off hard drive
      2007-ycal-4686-0006: Lost Roads Project - files for [text?]
      2007-ycal-4686-0007: broadsides, profiles, b'side list, essay
      2007-ycal-4686-0008: Sept 94 misc grabbag
      2007-ycal-4686-0009: BG 1
      2007-ycal-4686-0010: Cooling Time
      2007-ycal-4686-0011: everything off HD/pb 1400
      2007-ycal-4686-0012: Cooling Time (Palatine)
      2007-ycal-4686-0013: Cooling Time... (mostly) corrected long version
      2007-ycal-4686-0014: Applications EAB
      2007-ycal-4686-0015: The Leaves In Her Shoes, JL Jacobs
      2007-ycal-4686-0016: LRP Project odds & ends
      2007-ycal-4686-0017: The Interviews
      2007-ycal-4686-0018: Lila Wallace
      2007-ycal-4686-0019: [Send?] p.s.
      2007-ycal-4686-0020: Untitled
      2007-ycal-4686-0021: faculty bulletin
      2007-ycal-4686-0022: Josie's short & long things
      2007-ycal-4686-0023: taggart [ms?] credit line
      2007-ycal-4686-0024: Tremble, 1-21-95
      2007-ycal-4686-0025: Law school one
      2007-ycal-4686-0026: Poems disk, Trumble...
      2007-ycal-4686-0027: Business disk
      2007-ycal-4686-0028: C.V. & bio, CD Wright
      2007-ycal-4686-0029: Tremble hard disk
      2007-ycal-4686-0030: Correspondence 1994-1995
      2007-ycal-4686-0031: CV etc., Spg 95
      2007-ycal-4686-0032: The Leaves In Her Shoes, converted, 27 July 98
      2007-ycal-4686-0033: Poetry month, LRP contribution
      2007-ycal-4686-0034: interview w [Rosen?]
      2007-ycal-4686-0035: disinfectant
      2007-ycal-4686-0036: Lost Roads Pubs
      2007-ycal-4686-0037: hp deskjet 350 installation
      2007-ycal-4686-0038: brother disk 1 of 2, version B, Textbridge OCR
      2007-ycal-4686-0039: brother disk 2 of 2, version B, Textbridge OCR
      2007-ycal-4686-0040: Mule Reserve poetry, 7-98
      2007-ycal-4686-0041: Bewlefield, 5-99
      2007-ycal-4686-0042: brother Multi-Function Link... Disk 1, Version B
      2007-ycal-4686-0043: brother Multi-Function Link... Disk 2, Version B
      2007-ycal-4686-0044: Cole Heinowitz translation
      2007-ycal-4686-0045: LaserWriter
      2007-ycal-4686-0046: LaserWriter
      2007-ycal-4686-0047: LaserWriter, Disk 1
      2007-ycal-4686-0048: LaserWriter, Disk 3
      2007-ycal-4686-0049: LaserWriter, Disk 2
      2007-ycal-4686-0050: Eudora e-mail
      2007-ycal-4686-0051: Truitt promo matter
      2007-ycal-4686-0052: Iowa City files, spg 98 syllabus
      2007-ycal-4686-0053: new poems & other writing
      2007-ycal-4686-0054: letters & business
      2007-ycal-4686-0055: Disk#1, 1.2 MB, Anamorfosis Eisenhower
      2007-ycal-4686-0056: Wright.C, Wright.Q
      2007-ycal-4686-0057: C D Wright
      2007-ycal-4686-0058: letters - press (Brown)
      2007-ycal-4686-0059: poetics disk
      2007-ycal-4686-0060: MacSlip (1)
      2007-ycal-4686-0061: josiah
      2007-ycal-4686-0062: MacSlip, MacSlip Helper
      2007-ycal-4686-0063: 1995 fall syllabus
      2007-ycal-4686-0064: misc Aug 26 96
      2007-ycal-4686-0065: misc - everything, Brom hd questionnaire
      2007-ycal-4686-0066: misc (many recs)
      2007-ycal-4686-0067: Untitled
      2007-ycal-4686-0068: Untitled
      2007-ycal-4686-0069: Untitled
      2007-ycal-4686-0070: Untitled
      2007-ycal-4686-0071: Games
      2007-ycal-4686-0072: MacComCenter fax and data communications
      2007-ycal-4686-0073: Interim Pool report
      2007-ycal-4686-0074: DW 6.0
      2007-ycal-4686-0075: Back up disk 7
      2007-ycal-4686-0076: Back up disk 9
      2007-ycal-4686-0077: Back up disk 11
      2007-ycal-4686-0078: Back up disk 10
      2007-ycal-4686-0079: Systems back up disk 2
      2007-ycal-4686-0080: Systems back up disk 3
      2007-ycal-4686-0081: Systems back up disk 4
      2007-ycal-4686-0082: Back up disk 5
      2007-ycal-4686-0083: Back up disk 6
      2007-ycal-4686-0084: Back up disk 8
      2007-ycal-4686-0085: Back up disk 12
      2007-ycal-4686-0086: Back up disk 13 / Systems
      2007-ycal-4686-0087: Back up disk 14 / Systems
      2007-ycal-4686-0088: CD Rom Setup Version 5.3.2
      2007-ycal-4686-0089: Systems / Back up disk 1
      2007-ycal-4686-0090: baby x Eureka '90...
      2007-ycal-4686-0091: lover halpern Oct 87...
      2007-ycal-4686-0092: Tuscany poseidon...
      2007-ycal-4686-0093: LR catalog 88
      2007-ycal-4686-0094: Lane proposal
      2007-ycal-4686-0095: Helicon 9, ProJoGa3...
      2007-ycal-4686-0096: Connell memoir
      2007-ycal-4686-0097: many poems, letters, morrow...
      2007-ycal-4686-0098: Evan S. Connell memoir
      2007-ycal-4686-0099: bluedick Dec 87
      2007-ycal-4686-0100: Blue Dick #2, p.78-
      2007-ycal-4686-0101: New Blue Dick, July 88
      2007-ycal-4686-0102: newblue 2, original, July 88
      2007-ycal-4686-0103: New Blue 1, #11 copy, July 88
      2007-ycal-4686-0104: newblue 2 copy
      2007-ycal-4686-0105: bluedick #2 copy
      2007-ycal-4686-0106: Email 1-5-06
      2007-ycal-4686-0107: CDW Desktop 1-8-06
      2007-ycal-4686-0108: email sent items to 4-26-06, gen writing
  - Oversize
    - One Big Self Material, 2003, undated (Box 18 (Oversize))
    - Poems, 1984-2000, undated (Box 18 (Oversize))
    - Wide Open: Poetry in the Larger World, undated (Box 18 (Oversize))
    - Barbara Barg, 1978, undated (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Philip Booth, 1985-1996, undated (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Family, 1973-2005, undated (Box 19 (Oversize))